This time we update our Chrome extension, previously what we did, with all of the search engines,
categorized by countries. Everything is in the background,
we see it's torting cast engines, AI engines. So we have an eye edges,
now at a few categories. In this video it will be two charity search engines and
kids search engines, and I will just use the data from Austin Handbook with this open source,
and we have a search engines and here we have a code search children friendly search engines.
And this time we can try to actually look for it, have a five monster kid, top monster wacky say.
All right, so we'll use this two categories first to search for it. I use general search engine,
AI and other indexed one, I will use extract only domains, and I will open each one,
except I think the x on top marks is great additional resource, and then I will use this
website, so this one seems to not working. I'll type something like a test,
and now I'll use wacky say I will type test, I'll type test, I'll type test, I'll type test,
I'll type test, here as well, and top marks, I'll type test without selecting anything.
So now we have a few examples here, in order to use it, I will just copy it over to new agent,
so my new agent will be about, I will not name it now, I will just copy the kid search,
I will copy each other's URL with the test, and the test will be just our query, which is
built your queue that obviously is being populated because this one has queue, this has query,
and we want to copy the other's URL we hope as because as you can see search test, queue
equals to test, this one is even more advanced because you have PHP that queue equals to test,
search kids search, and now we'll use as well the top marks, and when I have it,
I will add a new category such as engines, but name it kids search engines,
and use this search engines, with test as a queue, text via, as a queue, searchable query,
URL as accused, okay, I think I need to ask for a total list, so I will just look for how
it can go, you can probably see some changes, so it's reviewing the current structure of it,
and now we do add, so you probably just create another, this is the kid search engines,
and we see search queue queue with different various locations, that's pretty perfect,
I will keep, I will now go to my main, and as well extension because it's just not only variable,
so if I add it already, then I will choose it and free, I can close it,
now we'll just open unpacked, I will use the Chrome extension, also in searcher,
it's now available, and now when it's available, I can go to any word,
for example, maybe I'll just open a hacker in your tabs, and if I'm interested in maybe
there is no longer a save heaven, who is the heaven, maybe something like a nice word, like
Gitia, or fail to ban, okay, let me, I will use brain word, and now I can use my search with
and we see kids search engine, that's perfect, and if I type it, we see brain and it's
such as that's perfect, now I'll try another one, search, I will use the kids search engine, wacky
save, and now I will use another one, so maybe, okay, now it's another one, the one was wacky save,
now fuck monster, and now I can use it again, kiddo, and kids search, having added a future that
if I press me the most button, you will just try to open all of the tabs with the current, so we can
quickly see actually how it looks like, so now if I go here with another one, top marks,
we see the brain is working, the brain here, okay, didn't refresh, this is one of you fresh,
this one refreshed, this one refreshed, and the brain here works as well, perfectly, wow, that's
nice, and I can open you agent, if I press my little mouse button on some category, try to search
with all tabs there in the folder and ask if I want to open multiple tabs, it's by default,
by Google, so just provide it, and naming them all just provide as well, another euros,
because why not, we made it for children, so we made for charity to, why not, let's use the
charity with such engine, I'll extract all the domains, and now we'll use some of it, I think this
one, this one, this one, this one, this one, a good search, and I think you care, right, so now
we'll just tap test for each one, okay, this one just works on the Chrome extension, so I will not
use it, the German one, ocean hero, saving the ocean, so he's different, Louisiana, all right,
I go, which is, I think one of the most popular, give a roll, and now we use give a worker,
now we test, always good search, and how we use video, and you care work, all right, so now,
means ready, I want to number that, add another category, but charity, name maybe charity,
and use this, these addresses, with tests in euro, and we will copy the thing that we actually made it,
so the first will be in good search, I'll open new tab, so it will be faster, okay, so this one,
we'll copy another one, ocean hero today, so once that working, I will skip it,
I'll use echo, I just want the most popular, I don't want to delete, I'll press shift,
press tap, this is give her actually quite complicated, I'm glad that we have checked, and this
will be in the region, and how we use the email, it's one of these friends, probably resource
being French, but it's okay, and I'll add this one, it's great, so it should add a new model,
here as you can see, it adds some to root categories, when it will open, the action will check,
so obviously there is just one entry, it will not ask and do it just open, all right, I've seen it somewhere,
so this is the new charity create extensions, so entrance, and this is the variable, those are,
so in free spaces, get search engines, sub menu, and here we have a possibility with search entry,
and now we will get some ID that actually indicates with errors, and it's mapped, all right,
I think it's ready, so I will go again to my Chrome extension, as you can see, everything goes open
there, and now I will close, a club starts to the right, I will just refresh it, I will go again
to one of the articles and harkenos, and now for example, I use heredic, all right, it doesn't matter,
now if I use charity, I see it's a good search, okay, it's talking, that's perfect,
I'll try maybe another one, let me try the biggest one, which is
a cobgia, and we can try that French one, just in case to see if it works, so such with we see
below, and this way we can look for it, that's pretty perfect, right, I love it, I love it, it looks
very good, but I will just add a few changes, and so the one will be probably, I don't like
the way him, it's named, because if I ask it, we see in just charity, I will say charity search engines,
and if I close it, this time I will add charity search engines, rename charity to try
to search engines, and another agent, when I press middle mouse button on the folder,
it doesn't open multiple paths or problems, the decision window, because it's not working,
and I want to get it done before I close this video, so we see it's checking the current
implementation, and the middle mouse button, action issue, so it will just change our background,
so it's planning, okay, it adds some console locks probably for debugging,
okay, it's moving the category 100 to the run first before the other hand doesn't
improve your handling, it's pretty nice, okay, it's not working with the duplicate,
my turn now is just to go to, now reload and see if it works, I'll go back to extension,
it's the refresh, and I will just try and do this heretic, and now search, we see the charity
search engine works, and now we have a closure here, so maybe I'll just hand, okay, it works,
and I think the charity a closure is still here, so I will just remove it from charity,
and from charity removal closure, because you have in the main route,
from charity, and closure, because I have an entry in the main route folder,
and we can even open new agent and ask, for example, how can I improve this?
extension, and what could be added, so we can even ask about possible updates,
that list is just too much for me, it's just in eight seconds, mobile is super responsible,
but we have possibly to that. Every once, pop up UI, error handling, enable disabled engines,
custom engine, order, yeah, you can beat it up, it doesn't reach, so you cannot pin agent,
because I would like to see this improvement, so I can always come back and read
about possible improvements for my Chrome extension.